

MIKHAIL BOBROV

frontend developer

CONTACTS

Yekaterinburg, Russia mikhailurban13@yandex.ru 89221481487

PROFILE

I am working with html/css/js starting from the 2019.

My current stack of technologies is: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Sass, Git, Gulp.

I am studying JS with Vladilen Minin, Alex Luschenko, HTML Academy and Wes Boss.

ABOUT ME:

For more than 10 years I have been working as a lawyer in a state organization. In addition, in 2016, I took up the profession of manage in social media marketing. I set up targeted ads. In 2019, I started learning html, css, java Script. I constantly study with the best specialists in this field. I'm currently looking for my first job in the world of web development

I prefer a healthy lifestyle.

In my spare time I am studying css with Rachel Andrew, Java-Script with Wes Boss, doing self- development activities.

I am free of the bad habits.

I have an experience in public speaking (starting from 9 up to 150 audience).

I have a son - Lev, he is 2 years old, and wife - Nastya

I have a pug)

Also I have experience in social media marketing

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

CitiBank banking and product consultant, B2B, Manpower CIS

JULY 2007 - MARCH 2008

Intasa Bank banking and product consultant, Bank Intesa

MARCH 2008 - MAY 2009

Military service, Russian Federation

JUNE 2009 - JUNE 2010

Lawer, Prosecutor's office

JUNE 2010 - PRESENT

Self-employed

MAY 2019 - PRESENT

I make websites using HTML, CSS, JS, GULP, Figma, SASS

EDUCATION

specialist, Ural State Law Academy, Yekaterinburg, Russia

2004 - 2009

1 Level, HTML Academy - ProfessionalHTML & CSS, level 1

SEPTEMBER 2019 - DECEMBER 2019

Level 2, HTML Academy - ProfessionalHTML & CSS, level 2

DECEMBER 2019 - MARCH 2020

Level 1, HTML Academy - Professional JavaScript

MARCH 2019 - JUNE 2020

Aleksandr Luschenko Java-Script course 2.0

APRIL 2020 - JULY 2020

LINKS

GitHub Linkedin GitHub

SKILLS

Git

HTML/CSS/JavaScript Gulp

Figma PHP Storm

SASS

LANGUAGES

English Russian

COURSES

Alexander Lushenko - ΟΟΠ (object oriented programming)

AUGUST 2020 - OCTOBER 2020

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Java-Script practice

AUGUST 2020 - PRESENT

HOBBIES

I have family, all my free time I spending with my wife - Nasty and son - Lev (like a Lion)

REFERENCES

Mikhail Bobrov

mikhailurban13@yandex.ru | 89221481487